(Sheldon:)the original purpose
of the appendix, Leonard?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)I do. And yet I'm doomed
(Sheldon:)while you live on.
(Leonard:)Funny how things
work out, isn't it?
(Sheldon:)Oh, Lord, I think
it's about to burst!
(Sheldon:)On the other hand,
(Sheldon:)it might have been
the Brussels sprouts.
(Leonard:)Good night.
(Sheldon:)Appendicitis.
(Sheldon:)What a nervous Nelly.
Penny! Penny!
Penny!
(Penny:)Coming, coming.
(Penny:)Hey, nice knees.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)They're my mother's.
(Penny:)Oh.
And the Flash
shirt is what?
Because, what,
you're gonna run really fast?
(Sheldon:)No, the Flash shirt is
because it's Friday,
(Sheldon:)but it's nice when
things work out.
(Sheldon:)Where's your
heart rate monitor?
I don't have one.
(Sheldon:)What about your pedometer?
Don't have one.
(Sheldon:)Do you have telematics
in your shoes connected
to an iPod?